Narrator: 19
Speaker: beautiful ugly
Narrator: 2
Speaker: big small
Narrator: 7
Speaker: cheap expensive
Narrator: 4
Speaker: clean dirty
Narrator: 5
Speaker: easy difficult
Narrator: 9
Speaker: fast slow
Narrator: 6
Speaker: full empty
Narrator: 1
Speaker: good bad
Narrator: 18
Speaker: high low
Narrator: 17
Speaker: hot cold
Narrator: 20
Speaker: light dark
Narrator: 11
Speaker: long short
Narrator: 14
Speaker: old new
Narrator: 16
Speaker: old young
Narrator: 15
Speaker: rich poor
Narrator: 13
Speaker: right left
Narrator: 12
Speaker: right wrong
Narrator: 3
Speaker: safe dangerous
Narrator: 8
Speaker: the same different
Narrator: 10
Speaker: strong weak
Narrator: 21
Speaker: tall short